I want to know and Akshay, I will tell you its buying price.
He has bought ICICI LBRD at the level of 340 340
and I would say that this is a great level of
buying.  You will see that the profit is a
huge profit.  Tell me, when there is such a
huge profit then we don't understand
what opinion we should give.  But still
Akshay, tell me how much should be invested in this bumper profit
?
Yes, you have made a very good entry
and according to me, there is
no need for you to lock in profits from this
because technically I am looking at the long term picture
because this is a long term
investment holding of yours, so here we are getting
clarity that 1700 is a
new support base
defined by ICICI LBRD on the long term charts.  However,
after a slight recovery in my opinion for the past 34 months, the stock has been
confined within a range.  But the kind of
technical setup it is, it seems that if
held from a long term horizon, then the all time
high of around 2300 will be its first potential
target and after that if that
breakout is also seen then perhaps the
stock can touch 2500 or 2600.  So
for the long term horizon, this is definitely a
hold.  1700 This
is your new support base.  If you want to take the trail stop loss approach then
1650 will be your trail stop loss
but hold from long bottom and
I believe that huge gains can be made from 2500 to 2600, these potential targets in the coming years.